Rise and shine!
Welcome to Mori-O-Radio.
As usual, this is your host, Kai Harada,
keeping you company on this fine morning,
and I've got just the song
to start you off right.
Now, let's dig in, shall we?
Oh, but before we begin, I have
a little something for you.
Thank you.
What can I just share with you?
What can I do with myself?
What can I do with you?
It's a huge dream.
I know it's a giant bolt.
It's a giant bolt.
It's a giant
bolt.
I'll chase you!
I'll chase you tomorrow!
I'll do it again!
I'll change the future!
So I'll chase you!
For last minute but would you be
interested in getting lunch with us?
Apologies but I must decline.
I need to finish delivering these
documents before the day gets away from me.
Enjoy your lunch!
Don't waste your time on
him he'd suck the life
out of the party the guys
and I invite him out.
On occasion but we can never tell
if he's having fun or hates us?
Yoshikage Kira age 33. Every single.
He's a model employee,
that's for damn sure.
But the guy's dull as dishwater.
It's not that he's necessarily
a tool or anything.
He's just kind of blah, you know?
Oh, is that right?
Someone's a little bent out of shape.
Some new girls at work
invited me to lunch.
Really, it's as innocent as that.
But I promised you lunch
was our time together.
I'd never go back in my word
just to fraternize with them.
You heard me turn them down, didn't you?
In the time we've known each other,
I've never left you by your lonesome.
Right?
Good, it's settled.
Now stop this silly fretting and
let's pick out some sandwiches.
Now, which one do you want?
This one has a delicate texture.
This bakery's one of my favorites.
It makes sandwiches with
bread made fresh at 11 a .m.
They're all the rage around here.
You'd be lucky to find one
on the shelf after 1 p .m.
Even through the wrapper, you can
feel they're fresh from the oven.
The katsu they use is always
freshly fried and perfectly crispy.
What have we here?
It seems in all the excitement, you managed
to tear the wrapper and make a mess.
Such a naughty girl.
It's a waste, but this
sandwich is ruined now.
I suppose we'll just
buy the one underneath.
Thank you for dropping by.
Simply beautiful, isn't it?
Quaint little Mario between us, it might
be the most marvelous town on earth!
It's like we're on a romantic picnic,
a
bit
aromatic for? my taste.
I think it's time for the
two of us to part ways.
The end is close at
hand.
Close at hand.
If luck is on my side,
perhaps I'll cross paths with a beautiful
new girl visiting from out of town.
Oh joy, it's a mutt.
Oh Huh?
Shigechi!
Hey!
Josuke and Okuyasu, good
to see you! What's up?
You know, you got here
just in the nick of time.
I'll get right to the point, okay?
We need to borrow some lunch money.
We're a little strapped
for cash at the moment.
Huh?
How's that even possible?
What happened to the money we
got from the lottery ticket?
Is it gone already?
Don't be silly.
We put all that in the bank.
And you gotta be crazy
if you think we go all
the way to the bank just
to get some munch money.
It's not worth the walk.
A thousand yen should be
enough for both of us.
I agree.
Come on, as soon as school's over,
we'll head to the bank and pay you back.
Hey, I know that logo.
You got a sandwich from St.
Gentleman, didn't you?
Well, what do you know?
I thought they were sold out.
They are, and you're not getting a
single bite of mine, you got that?
If you leave my sandwich alone,
I'll lend you guys the money.
Sweet, I can taste their lunch already.
Thank you.
And just so you know,
I'm writing an I .O .U.
for this little loan.
You're not gonna weasel out of this one.
Me?
You're the biggest weasel there is.
Okay, June 24th, lend
1,000 yen to needy friends.
Hang on. Lent.
How do you write the
character for Lent again?
Oh, well.
This'll work for now.
I guess Hiragana's better than nothing.
Crud, monkeys.
I don't know how to write
Josuke or Okuyasu either.
Huh? What the?
My sandwich was right there.
Where did it go?
What a relief.
My sandwich is safe and sound.
I don't remember it being this far
away, Hey, but at least I found it.
Th-that's...
Hey Josuke Okuyasu, wait up!
We're not done yet!
I need your thumb prints on my
I .O .U to make it official!
You have got to be kidding me.
That lump of a brat
grabbed my back by mistake.
Come on, could you be any more annoying?
How would we give you our thumbprints?
It's simple.
You cut your thumb with a
knife and use the blood.
What are you talking about?
We don't have to go that far.
Just sign the IOU and we'll call it good.
Yeah, yeah, but let's haul ass to St.
Gentleman before they sell out.
Damn it.
I can't let him see what's in that bag.
She's still wearing the ring I
put on her finger this morning.
It has my fingerprints on it.
So when the police open an investigation,
it'll be just a matter of time
before they trace it back to me.
Yoshikage Kira has been
at this for 15 years,
and in all that time, he's
never left a single clue.
This pathetic whelp isn't changing that.
Hey, Josuke, let's head in. Right.
I'll stay outside and wait for you guys.
My best bet is to take it by force.
On second thought, I'd better
snatch it without his knowing.
Shigechi!
You're a lucky son of
a gun, you know that?
The lunchtime rush beat us here
and they're already out of St.
Gentleman's sandwiches.
Just our luck.
They're sold out, huh?
Well, isn't that a shame?
I feel bad for you guys, I really do.
I guess I could sell you mine, but so
you know it'll cost you 10,000 yen, okay?
Boy, not a decent bone
in your body, is there?
All right, Josuke, looks
like we're headed to Hokuben.
You sure that'll be enough?
I doubt a 500 yen meal and
a drink will fill us up.
We're better off skipping it.
It's not my first choice, but
the cafeteria will do just fine.
Besides, that's where Koichi
said he's getting lunch today.
Oh man, that means he'll be
there with Yukako Yamagishi.
I hate having to be the third wheel
to those honeymooners' love fest.
And the food they serve is terrible.
Their nasty meat is so thin,
it's practically invisible.
And who knows what kind of weird
shit they put in the Masa soup.
Hey, why don't we use the equipment
room in my middle school's gym?
It has tons of drinks to choose from.
Our PE teacher always
sneaks away to have his
coffee and tea in there
when no one's looking.
All the teachers are in the
faculty room during lunch,
so they won't be able to bust us.
Sometimes I'll sneak in through the
window and take a cup to quench my thirst.
Why don't you go buy lunch and we'll
hang out there and eat together?
Let's back it up there, Shigechi.
Are you seriously stealing
drinks from school?
You stingy bastard!
Can't you even buy drinks for yourself?
You've never seen me doing
something that greedy.
See you later.
Geez, what crawled up there butts?
I was just trying to be nice.
Okay, well, you better pay me
back my thousand yen tomorrow.
Sorry for bumping into you sir it's all my
fault I wasn't looking where I was going.
Sorry again shit so close he's left his
idiotic friends but he's heading back to
school he's eating
lunch there so what's my
next move I believe
they call him Shigechi.
Minutes from now he'll open that
bag and things will get very
complicated.
Damn it, this is unfathomable.
Alrighty,
now that I'm in my special hiding spot,
I can finally eat my lunch in peace.
Oh, yeah!
How did I almost forget?
Before I start chowing down on
my food, I need to make coffee.
It's not a secret trip to the
gym without a freshly brewed cup.
Fortune has smiled on you, Shigechi.
Had you peeked inside, my only recourse
would have been to obliterate you.
Josuke, I think this is the place.
It's smaller than I thought. What the?
Why are they here?
I thought these two were blowing them off.
Shigechi!
You here or what?
Shigechi! Huh?
Hey, what are you doing here?
I thought you were going to
get lunch somewhere else.
That was the plan.
We couldn't just pass up
free coffee from Cafe Gym.
We got 500 yen Mega
nochi bentos on the way!
Wow!
I can't believe you two actually showed up
to eat after calling me a stingy bastard.
You're a couple of hypocritical pricks.
Come on, man, cut us some slack.
Haven't you heard of people
changing their minds?
It is a thing that happens, you know.
Now what do I do?
Offing one of them would
be a walk in the park,
but I can't tackle all three at once.
Shit, I was so close, too.
She's only centimeters away.
Shigechi, you mind grabbing
me a drink on your way back?
And could you make it a
green tea instead of coffee?
I'll take a black tea with milk. Really?
Makunochi with milk tea?
That sounds disgusting.
Shit, he's going to try to eat his
meal right on top of this thing.
If I don't do something fast, he's going
to open the bag right in front of them.
Ah, not soy sauce again.
They're always giving me
soy sauce with katsu. Huh?
That's how you're supposed to eat it.
No way. Don't be stupid.
Everyone knows it's tonkatsu sauce.
Putting soy sauce on tonkatsu
violates all that sacred.
Like it matters.
Yes.
Damn it.
What the hell?
Just a minute!
What exactly do you think you're doing?
Talk!
Because from where I'm standing,
it looks like you're trying to
steal my sandwich out from under me!
As if.
Stop being such an idiot.
I came over here because I
thought I heard something weird.
I was going to check it out
and then get back to eating.
My food's off limits, hear me?
I can already hear your sappy sob story.
Teriyaki chicken
sandwiches are my favorite,
so won't you please give me
a teeny-weeny bite, Shigechi?
Tell me I'm wrong, you can't, can you?
Ugh, you sure are a greedy
little stinker, aren't you?
Why don't you focus on
bringing out my tea?
Oh, and don't forget my milk tea!
I'm making them fast as I can!
Now!
Huh?
I did it.
Hey, get them while they're hot.
One green tea and one black
tea with milk. Oh! Thanks.
What's with you?
My sandwich disappeared!
What did you lunch thieves do with it?
Lunch thieves? Who, us?
It's definitely gone.
But we didn't have anything to do with it.
Tell him, Okuyasu, what he said.
I've had enough of your games!
There's no one else here but us!
You gotta know what
happened to my sandwich!
We don't.
Seriously, we're telling you the truth.
Yeah, cross our hearts.
We're not messing around.
We're just as confused
about all this as you are.
Phew, lying punks. Fine.
Now you gotta make me angry.
It's the truth.
I've had enough of you
pointing the finger at us.
Why would we take your sandwich
when we've got our own?
If you're gonna lie, then
we'll do things my way!
All I have to do is make Harvest
turn this room inside out!
Damn, you are so annoying!
Fine, fine, search the room.
I want you to, search until
you pass out, go for it.
For the last time, why would
we steal a stupid sandwich?
This is torture, what's
going on out there?
I can't see a thing trapped under here.
I don't know what that pissant is up
to, but it can't be anything good.
Hey, open up, I know somebody's in here.
Shit balls were busted!
It's the PE teacher!
Crap!
Then it's time to bail!
Let's go!
I can't leave!
I still haven't found my sandwich!
Now's not the time!
Ouchie-go!
Get back here!
Let's beat it!
No good, hooligans.
I thought my tea and coffee
wasn't lasting very long.
I thought I was going crazy,
but I was just being used.
I have to start locking this
place up tighter than Fort Knox.
This day has been hellacious,
but despite every setback, I beat
the odds and have been reunited
with my girl.
I can't explain it, but I've always had
the feeling that somewhere out there
is a guardian angel looking
over Yoshikage Kira's shoulder.
That in the end, things
will work out for the best.
And if I live every day with rigor and
boldness, I'll ultimately be delivered from
a wretched life.
We had a pretty close call today, my dear,
but I knew we'd find our way back to each
other.
I found it.
Now why is someone I've never laid
eyes on skulking off with my sandwich?
And while we're on this subject buster,
why is some strange man hanging around my
school like It's another
day at the office.
Pardon?
You wouldn't happen to be talking
to me, would you, little boy?
Because I haven't the faintest
idea what you're going on about.
If you must know, I just
purchased this item at St.
Gentleman.
You can save the bullshit
that bags my property.
I could go on and on about
how I know it's mine,
but someone like you
would never understand.
Time to take back what's ours, Harvest!
Blasted!
What the hell is happening?
The bag's being ripped away.
Wait, what? No way.
I don't understand what's going on.
That's not my sandwich.
Oh, god.
Did that ham come from a real person?
So it's come to this, eh?
My secret is out.
Interestingly enough, you
and I, it would appear.
That we both share a unique power but how?
What did you just say?
Can you see my harvest?
No, that's not.
Important right now?
Why are you strutting around
carrying a hand in your bag?
That's so freaky.
You're by yourself, I presume.
I don't see your playmates anywhere.
I believe their names
were Josuke and Okuyasu.
Would it be safe to assume they
both have powers similar to ours?
Oh no, don't you move a single muscle?
If you so much as blink, you're a gutter.
My gutsy and you're some kind of closet
weirdo and I don't want
you coming any closer.
So stay there.
If you know what's good for ya.
Just looking at your slimy face
is starting to make my skin crawl.
You're evil and evil people
need to stay far away.
You can call me Yoshikage Kira.
I'm currently 33 years old.
Not that you'd.
care, but I reside in Northeast
Morio's Villa District.
Also, I've yet to marry.
In order to make a living, I work
for Kameyo Department Stores.
After a long day's work,
I return home no later
than 8 p .m.
I don't like smoking, but do
enjoy the occasional drink.
I'm always in bed by 11 p .m.,
and I make it a point to get no less
than eight hours of sleep each night.
Before bed, I drink a warm glass of milk.
It's always coupled with 20 minutes of
stretching to decompress
from the long work day.
Sweet dreams are the usual result of this.
I then awake as refreshed and
recharged as a newborn child,
ready to take on the day's?
challenges.
And after my last checkup I was
given a clean bill of health.
Hey, what's the big idea, creeper?
Why are you telling me this crap?
For as long as I can remember,
I've done everything in my
power to live a productive
life that allows me to
pursue a lasting inner?
peace.
This may be a foreign concept,
but I choose not to concern
myself with winning or losing
life's troubles or enemies
who bring sleepless nights.
That is how I cope with this backwards
life we find ourselves living.
It's what brings me happiness in a
world fraught with hardship and misery.
Of course, if I were
ever to engage in combat,
I would win the battle without question.
In other words, Shigechi,
you are an irksome troublemaker
who stands to hinder my sleep.
You, boy, are the enemy.
Deadly queen.
I named it myself, and truth be
told, I'm quite proud of the moniker.
But before you have the chance to
utter a word of this to another soul,
I shall eradicate you.
I'll sleep soundly tonight.
I can already feel it.
Anytime I need to see your
face, it has closed my eyes?
And I am taken to a place
where you're crystal mine.
I'm a gentle feeling, take a
shelter in the face of my spine,
straight like a Chaka cherry cola.
I don't need to try to explain, I just
hold on tight, and if it happens again,
I'ma move so slightly to
the arms and the lips and
the face of the humic and
the ball that I need to,
I want to.
Come and stand a little bit closer,
breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you.
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you, but ooh,
I've got to find out.
Ooh,
I want you, I don't know if I need
you, but ooh, I've got to find out.